#### **ADITTIA AGUSTIAN**

+628990364658 | agustianaa12adit@gmail.com | Linkedin Me | Karawang, Indonesia

# **SELF DESCRIPTION**



I am a graduate of Bachelor of Information Systems and have experience in IT Web Development and Full-Stack Web Development. I previously worked as a web developer on a research project at Buana Perjuangan University, collaborating with professors and the IT Web Development team to create websites. Apart from that, I volunteered on the COVID-19 vaccination IT team in Karawang Regency and completed a 1 year internship in Full-Stack Web Development through the Certified Student Internship Program (PMMB) and the BUMN Talented Generation Internship Program (MAGENTA).

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Karawang Library** 12/11/2019 – 15/05/2020

# Building a Karawang Library Web System (Research and Internship)

- Design and design library web systems.
- Collaborate with the team to build a library web system.

# LP3M Buana Perjuangan University Karawang LP3M E-Cycle Web Development

15/06/2020 - 14/05/2021

- Collaborate with the team to develop the E-Cycle web.
- Improved features and improvements in the e-cycle web system.
- Make data designs, and programmers in developing e-cycle web.

# Covid-19 Vaccine IT Team Services and IT Support

02/06/2021 - 15/02/2022

- Collaborate with the team in conducting Covid-19 Vaccine IT services.
- Increasing the input of data on Covid-19 cases in Karawang Regency.
- IT Support in Vaccine and Covid-19 activities.

# PERUM PERURI

19/09/2022 - 28/02/2023

# **Full Stack Web Developer**

- Employee services, to serve the needs of each employee such as submitting evidence of reimbursement of costs, applying for doctor's leave, applying for leave permits, submitting active work certificates, PAKLARING, etc.
- Make a letter of guarantee for the manufacture of glasses.
- Create a web system for employee facilities.
- Creating Perum PERURI Employee Recreation Assistance System.
- Create an employee data web system for each subsidiary of Perum Peruri.

# PERUM PERURI

1/03/2023 - 31/08/2023

#### **Web Development**

- Development of the Employee Facility system.
- Development of PERUM PERURI employee recreation assistance system.
- Develop a web-based cost monitoring information system that aims to streamline the cost tracking process.
- Configure the server to implement the web system by making the necessary configurations on the XAMPP, SSH, and server IP settings.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Information Systems, Faculty of Computer Science Buana Perjuangan University, Karawang

Current Cumulative GPA: 3.93/4.00 Click to view

#### **ABILITY**

- Information System: Web Development, Database, User Experience, UML
- Programming language: PHP, Javascript, Python, SQL, MySQL
- Front End: CSS, HTML, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap and ReactJS
- Web Framework : Codeigniter Framework, Laravel Framework
- Design: CorelDraw, Figma, Photoshop
- Hard Skill: Web Development, Full Stack Developer, Data Science, Design, Configuration Server
- Soft Skill: Team Work, Adaptability, Attention to Detail, Collaboration, Problem Solving
- Tools used: Visual Studio Code, UML, XAMPP, MySQL WorkBench, Postman, Google Colab

## **PROJECTS / PORTFOLIO**

My Project Portfolio: My Portfolio

#### **CERTIFICATE**

- Web Development Group Competition (Sriwijaya University) : Click to View
- Training on Making Music Listening Application (Coding.id): <u>Click to View</u>
- Create Email Blast with Python (Coding.id): Click to View
- Basic Git Command Training (Coding.id): <u>Click to View</u>
- SQL Fundamental Course Training (Sololearn): <u>Click to View</u>
- React + Redux Course Training (Sololearn) : Click to View
- Covid-19 Volunteer Charter and Vaccination Kab. Karawang: Click to View
- BNSP Certification Web Development : <u>Click to View</u>
- Certified Student Internship Program (BUMN Perum Peruri) : Click to View
- Talent Generation Internship Program (MAGENTA): <u>Click to View</u>
- Laravel 9 basic training (Binary Campus): Click to View